// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question:"Five friends A, B, C, D, and E like different colors: Red, Blue, Green, Yellow, and Purple. Who likes the color Yellow?",
    answer: "B",
    options: [
      "B",
      "C",
      "D",
      "E"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: " Three brothers - Alan, Brian, and Chris - live in three different cities: New York, Los Angeles, and Chicago. Who lives in Chicago?",
    answer: "Chris",
    options: [
      "Chris",
      "Alan",
      "Brian",
      
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Emma, Jack, Lisa, Mark, and Sarah - participate in a spelling competition. Who spelled the word incorrectly?",
    answer: "Alan",
    options: [
      "Alan",
      "Emma",
      "Jack",
      "Lisa"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Alice, Ben, Clara, David, Emily, and Frank - participated in a running race. Who finished the race in the third position?",
    answer: "x > 8",
    options: [
      "Alice",
      "Ben",
      "clara",
      "David",
      "Emily",
      "Frank"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: " Four people - Alex, Brooke, Charlie, and Dylan - each have a different profession: Doctor, Engineer, Lawyer, and Teacher. Who is the Engineer?",
    answer: "Charlie",
    options: [
      "Alex",
      "Charlie",
      "Brook",
      "Dylan"
    ]
  },
  

     {
   numb: 6,
   question: "Five cars - Audi, BMW, Honda, Toyota, and Volkswagen - are parked in a row. Which car is parked in the middle?",
    answer: "Honda",
    options: [
      "Honda",
      "Benz",
      "BMW",
      "Audi"
    ]
   },
   {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Six people - Adam, Bella, Charlie, David, Eva, and Frank - are seated in a circle. Who is seated between Adam and Eva?",
     answer: "Eva",
     options: [
       "Bella",
       "charlie",
       "David",
       "Eva"
     ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "Five friends - George, Helen, Ian, James, and Kate - have different pets: Cat, Dog, Fish, Rabbit, and Turtle. Who has a Cat?",
       answer:"George",
       options: [
         "George" ,
         "Helen",
         "Ian",
         "James"
       ]
      },
      {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Four houses are colored in different colors: Blue, Green, Red, and Yellow. The house at the end is Blue. Which house is next to the Blue house?",
         answer: "Green",
         options: [
           "Green",
           "Blue",
           "Blue",
           "Black"
         ]
        },
        {
          numb: 10,
          question: "Seven friends - Alice, Bob, Carol, David, Emma, Frank, and Grace - are sitting in a row. Who is sitting in the middle?",
          answer: "Bob",
          options: [
            "Carol",
            "David",
            "Alice",
            "Bob"
          ]
          }
];